https://www.cryptomathic.com/creditsandprivacy

Creative common Credits list for images on Cryptomathic.com
Homepage :
Bank Vault - Credit:  User - sahobbit , "Vault Bank" Jan 13, 2016, via pixabay.com, Creative Commons Attribution.
Walrus - Credit:  User - skeeze , "Bull Walrus" June 12, 2010, via pixabay.com, Creative Commons Attribution.
White Papers, Image 1 - Credit:  User - 3112014 ,"Credit Card Payment" May 13, 2015 via pixabay.com, Creative Commons Attribution.
White Papers, Image 2 - Credit:  User - tec estromberg ,"happy business people clapping" Jan 28, 2009 via Flikr , Creative Commons Attribution.
Products, CSG- Credit:  User -ESA/S.Bierwald - "European Space Agency"  August 6, 2014, via flickr.com, Creative Commons Attribution.
Products, CKMS - Credit:  User -Steve wilson- "Business woman" July 8, 2009, via flickr.com, Creative Commons Attribution.
Products, CardInk - Credit:  User -FirmBee,  William Iven- "iphone with card"  Jan. 22, 2014, via pixabay.com, Creative Commons Attribution.
Industries page:
Industries, Banking - Credit:  User -Skeeze, "Canary Wharf" Oct. 12, 2015, via pixabay.com, Creative Commons Attribution.
Industries, Government - Credit:  User -Aotearoa ,  - "UN Members Flags"   Jun. 13, 2007, via wikimedia.com, Creative Commons Attribution.
Industries, Cloud - Credit:  User -Free-photos, "Suspension Bridge Golden "Jan. 22, 2014, via pixabay.com, Creative Commons Attribution.
Industries, Technology - Credit:  User -MasterTux , "microchip ic"  Jan. 22, 2017, via pixabay.com, Creative Commons Attribution.
Cryptomathic's Events, Banner - Credit: National Retail Federation , "Attendees at the 2013 BIG Show" May. 23, 2013, via commons.wikimedia.org, Creative Commons Attribution.
Terms of Use
BY USING THIS WEBSITE YOU ACCEPT THESE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE TERMS OF USE, THEN DO NOT USE CRYPTOMATHIC’S WEBSITE OR ANY OF ITS CONTENT OR SERVICES. THESE TERMS OF USE MAY BE AMENDED OR UPDATED BY CRYPTOMATHIC FROM TIME TO TIME WITHOUT NOTICE AND THE TERMS OF USE MAY HAVE CHANGED SINCE YOUR LAST VISIT TO THIS WEBSITE. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO REVIEW THESE TERMS OF USE FOR ANY CHANGES. YOUR USE AFTER ANY AMENDMENTS OR UPDATES OF THESE TERMS OF USE SIGNIFIES YOUR CONSENT TO AND ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH REVISED TERMS. ANY NEW FEATURES THAT MAY BE ADDED TO THIS WEBSITE FROM TIME TO TIME WILL BE SUBJECT TO THESE TERMS OF USE, UNLESS STATED OTHERWISE. YOU SHOULD VISIT THIS PAGE PERIODICALLY TO REVIEW THESE TERMS OF USE.
Privacy Policy
Cryptomathic (“we”/”us”/“our”) is committed to protecting your privacy. We make our website, https://www.cryptomathic.com (the “Website”) together with our Services available under the conditions set out in our Terms of Use immediately above. This Privacy Policy sets out how we collect, store and use information about our users through the Website and Services. The “Services” means use of the resources made available on our Website.
Consent
By using the Website or our Services you consent to the use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, your personal information will not be used for any other purpose without your consent. We will not collect Personal Information (as defined below) for purposes of sale or marketing in a way that identifies the individual; we do not sell customer lists. You may withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal information at any time by informing us in writing. However, withdrawing your consent may result in your inability to continue using the Website and/or the Services.
Withdrawing consent
If at any time you want to withdraw your consent to our storing and processing of your Personal Information, please send us an email to enquiry@Cryptomathic.com.
Collection of Information
We aim to collect, store and use only such Personal Information as is required to enable us (i) to manage your account and communication preferences, i.e. to help us provide tailored and relevant communications for you, (ii) to provide any services to you or your organization, (iii) to maintain our customer and / or Website visitor lists, (iv) to respond to your inquiries or provide feedback, (v) for identification and authentication purposes, and (vi) for service improvement. Cryptomathic only processes your Personal Information where we have lawful grounds and legitimate business reasons to do so. We will maintain the confidentiality of any Personal Information, including contact information, you provide to us and we will use such information only for the purposes for which we have collected it (subject to the exclusions and disclosures identified immediately below), unless you give your explicit consent to us that we may disclose such information to third parties.
Two types of information collected through the Website and our Services: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information
This Privacy Policy does not extend to the collection, storage, use or disclosure of the following information which is currently not limited by applicable privacy laws: (a) information that is publicly available, such as names, addresses, telephone numbers and electronic address when listed in a publicly available directory; or (b) Non-Personal Information (as defined below).
"Personal Information" is personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information, birth date and gender. It is always your choice whether or not to provide Personal Information but if you choose not to provide certain requested Personal Information, in some instances you may not be able to register to use the Website or access our Services. In other instances, your choice not to provide certain Personal Information may result in you not being able to use certain features of the Website or Services. We may collect Personal Information in respect of the Website or Services through registration; communications with you; information downloads; service use; purchases; user support; and surveys.
"Non-Personal Information" is information of an anonymous nature, such as an Internet Protocol Address (IP Address), the domain used to access the Website or Services, and the type and version of browser or operating system being used by users of the Website or Services. Aggregate information, such as number of visitors, pages accessed and average time spent on the Website constitutes Non-Personal Information, nor is general business contact information and information provided through your browser or stored in a cookie considered Personal Information.
Use of Personal Information
We collect information for the following purposes:
1. Registration: In order to access our Services you must provide certain Personal Information.
2. Metadata: We collect and use various metadata derived from your use of the Website and Services. In cases where content is made publicly available such as public comments, the associated metadata may also be made publicly available.
3. Location Information: If you enable location services on your computer or mobile device, we will collect and use information about your location.
4. Marketing Communications: If you opt in to receive news and marketing communications from us, we will keep you up to date on our products and services. You may withdraw your consent to receiving marketing communications from us at any time by following the opt out instructions in each communication.
5. Statistics: We collect statistics about use of the Website and Services which we use for analytics including predictive analytics. Aggregate statistics that do not personally identify an individual will be kept and used by us.
6. System Logs & Cookies (Cookie Policy): Cookies are used by us to track content usage and traffic on the Website. A cookie is a feature of your web browser that consists of a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. Cookies help us compile aggregate statistics about usage of this Website, such as how many users visit the Website, how long users spend viewing the Website, and what pages are viewed most often. This information is used to improve the content of the Website. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie. This gives you the option to decide whether or not to accept it. If you disable cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of the Website or Services.
7. Your IP address is reported by your web browser whenever you visit a page on the Website. This information is recorded together with your registration information in our databases.
If we plan to use your Personal Information in future for any other purposes not identified above, we will inform you by updating this Privacy Policy.
Relationship with third Parties
We may employ third parties to help us improve the Website. These third parties may have limited access to the Personal Information solely for the purpose of improving the Website. They will be subject to contractual restrictions prohibiting them from using the Personal Information for any other purpose. Furthermore, if Cryptomathic becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any Personal Information and provide notice before Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We use appropriate security measures to store and maintain your Personal Information in a secure environment and protect against unauthorized access and disclosure.
Retention
We will keep your Personal Information only for as long as it remains necessary for the identified purposes, which may extend beyond the termination of our relationship with you. All retained Personal Information will remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you request that your Personal Information be removed from our databases, it may not be possible to completely delete all your Personal Information due to technological constraints, however, in such circumstances we will refrain from contacting or actively using your Personal Information.
Access and Accuracy
You have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you in order to verify your Personal Information and to have a general account of our uses of that information. Upon receipt of your written request, we will provide you with a copy of your Personal Information.
Contact Us
You can help by keeping us informed of any changes, such as a change of contact details. Please contact us at enquiry@Cryptomathic.com.
It doesn't matter where you are. We can work anywhere in the world! And we would love to hear from you, be sure we will reply asap.
e: enquiry@cryptomathic.com t: + 45 8676 2288
HEADQUARTERSCryptomathic A/SJaegergardsgade 118DK-8000 Aarhus CDenmark
